Diego Maquill

Revere, MA 02151 | Cellular: 617-834-6182 | Email: diego.maquill@gmail.com
Portfolio: https://dmaquill-react-portfolio.herokuapp.com | GitHub: https://github.com/diego-maquill
LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/diego-m-24b4a8115

SUMMARY

Full-stack developer with a degree in Computer Science from Suffolk University and completed a Certificate as a Full Stack Developer from the Harvard Extension School. Most recent experience is working with website development in .NET #C MVC projects. Interested in problem solving tools and software development that can solve real live problems. Recognized by peers for combining clean and efficient design with excellent team work and customer service skills.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

NodeJS | jQuery | AJAX /APIs | React | MongoDB | Express | .NET | MySQL

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Kripto IT Inc. Boston MA Junior Software Developer

2018-Present

Effectively developed MVC websites and marketing tools in an Agile environment. ASP.NET Core 3.1 web applications Technologies: .NET, C# JavaScript, MySQL.

- Received accolades for writing documentation for coding modification.
- Recognized as a team player by manager and coworkers.

Solvima Graf Inc, Lima-Peru

Software Sales Specialist

Marketing and Development of web application. Involved in EF authentication design. Presenting web application capabilities to customers. Technologies: JavaScript, MySQL.

- English ← → Spanish language customization for web application.
- Presentation of software application for bilingual customers and users.

Harbor Health Services Inc. Mattapan, MA Human Resources Data Support Specialist

2007-2013

Effectively administered data for 500 employees in a MySQL database system. Daily responsibilities were executing queries in SQL for managers of different departments. Technologies: MySQL, Sage HR, SSRS reports.

- Recognized by manager for report accuracy.
- Created an instructions manual with commands to quickly create quarries for reporting.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Fast&Fresh | Github: https://github.com/diego-maquill/adding-react Link: https://dmaquill-react-portfolio.herokuapp.com

- Ecommerce web application for farmers market. It was made with the idea of connecting bypassing. buyers with rotating farmer's market in big cities throughout the US.
- Directed design and development from the ground up.
- Technologies: NodeJS, APIs, MongoDB, handlebars

EDUCATION

Full Stack Bootcamp Certificate - Harvard University Extension School

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science - Suffolk University

2013-2018